askpcexperts.com 2015-06-26

# Privacy Policy - AskPCExperts

**Have questions?** Let us answer them all!

Askpcexperts is committed to your privacy. The policy details how we utilize your personal identifying information. This privacy policy may be modified at any time without notice to you and covers the usage of your personal information by each and every business owned and operated by Askpcepxerts.com and its parent corporation, Cyber Futuristics (India) Pvt. Ltd. . Your personal identifying information may be stored or utilized by any and all businesses under the Cyber Futuristics (India) Pvt. Ltd. Penumbra but always within the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. 

Our privacy policy respects and recognizes your right to confidentiality and is committed to protecting the privacy of the visitors to its web site www.askpcexperts.com Askpcexperts is the sole owner of the information collected on www.askpcexperts.com. We will not provide, rent, loan, or sell any identifiable personal information to any other third party, unless legally required to do so. The information is collected from users at various different points on our website.

  1. **Personal Details**  
Before using the Askpcexperts Service, the customer must first complete the registration form. This involves giving user contact information such as First and Last name, E-mail address, Postal address, etc. Askpcexperts will use your contact details to contact you regarding the product and/or services you have requested. This consists of renewal/re-registration notifications, special offers, and surveys on improving our service. 
  2. **Payment Details**   
If user purchases a plan by Askpcexperts, we will collect credit card information, and other payment information necessary to complete a payment from user. Askpcexperts may use a third party to process and verify credit cards for billing purposes. This entails we share user name, credit card number, expiration date and billing address with the credit card processing company. When processing a payment transaction, Askpcexperts will also obtain information regarding the amount of the payment and other transaction data. We may transfer or disclose this payment information to a third party only to the extent necessary in order to complete the payment processing.
  3. **Computer System Information**
    1. **Subscriber Computer** \- We may also seek information related to your computer. This may include: information about the make and model of your computer and/or any computer hardware, software or peripherals attached to it, date of purchase and type of computer, identification number of your computer, condition of the computer and the application if reporting a fault occurrence and during diagnostics, system and registry data about software installations and hardware configurations, and error tracking files. Generally, this information is required to offer personalized technical support to you, and to help us update our support tools and augment our supported products list. 
    2. **Remote Access** \- While requesting support you may request for the problem to be resolved by taking control of your computer. Askpcexperts uses qualified utilities which allow user to grant control of user computer to an Expert remotely over the Internet, so that the Expert can diagnose or correct problems. Experts are not allowed to use the Remote Access software until and unless they have received adequate training in its use, and user have consented to grant control. Furthermore, Experts will not use Remote Access tools to collect sensitive or confidential information stored on user computer or network, deliberately destroy information on user computer or network, or cause user to experience system problems.
    3. **Diagnostic Tool** \- Some Askpcexperts online diagnoses applications may gather a broad variety of functional information about the state of a computer system and the applications on it. This information is packaged into a document containing all the essential details needed by Askpcexperts and is transmitted securely over the Internet to the Askpcexperts server. Askpcexperts analyzes this information to help diagnose and solve end-user problems. Information collected by the Askpcexperts application will not contain any sensitive information such as e-mail messages, e-mail addresses sent to, passwords, profiles, websites visited, etc.

Use of the Remote Access and Diagnoses applications is also subject to the terms of use in the respective software license agreements

  4. **Cookies**   
A cookie is a message given to a web browser by a web server. The browser stores the message in a text file. The main idea of cookies is to identify users and possibly prepare customized web pages for them. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site and cannot violate the privacy of our customers. 
  5. **Live Help Session Records**  
Askpcexperts reserves the right to monitor on-line and off-line sessions between user and a Tech Support Executive for quality control of the service provided to the customer by Tech Support Executive. Moreover, we may record on-line and off-line sessions conducted on the Web site for user reference and to assist in resolution of disputes and/or potential complaints. The session records will also be used to improve the service, build a support knowledge base, and/or conduct internal market research. Session record data will, however, not be correlated with personally identifiable data about individual customers. 
  6. **Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, track user movement, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 
  7. **Sharing**   
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 
  8. **Contests and Surveys**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from user via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is entirely voluntary and user therefore, has a choice whether or not to divulge this information. Information requested may include contact information such as name and shipping address, and demographic information such as zip code. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Security Issues**  
Our site uses all precautions to protect information of users. This Web site takes every precaution to protect information of users. Whenever sensitive information is submitted by the user via the website, it is protected both on-line and off-line. Sensitive information such as credit card number is encrypted and is protected with the best of the encryption software. We use industry-standard 128bit encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. Similarly equivalent care is undertaken to protect user-information off-line. The entire information of our users, including the sensitive information outlined above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees like billing clerk or a customer service representative who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Even they use password-protected screen-savers each time they leave their workstations. On return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept abreast on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter and any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to make sure our customers' information is protected. Lastly, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a highly secure environment. 

Other sites accessible through our web site have their own security and privacy policies and data collection practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. In situations that are required by law and to safeguard ourselves in any legal action, we may disclose some information about our users to law-enforcing officers.

**Auxiliary Information**   
In order for this Web site to properly accomplish its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from Third party sources.

  1. **Special Offers** \- We send all new members a welcoming e-mail to verify password and logon name. Older members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and newsletters.
  2. **Correction/Updating Personal Information** \- If User's personally identifiable information changes (such as user zip code), or if User no longer desire the Service, we will Endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove User personal data provided to us. This can be done at the Profile page.
  3. **Notification of Changes** \- Askpcexperts reserves complete right to update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting changes online without any notice to you. The most current version of the Privacy Policy can be reviewed by clicking on the "Privacy Policy" hypertext link located on our website http://www.Askpcexperts.com. It is your responsibility to refer to this Privacy Policy before submitting any information on the website. Submitting your information after such changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those posted changes.
  4. If at any point we choose to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify user via e-mail. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Please contact us if you should have any questions, comments or concerns about this privacy policy.

Disclaimer AskPCExperts is an independent service provider of remote tech support for third party products. Any use of third party trademarks mentioned on this site, brand names, products and services is only referential and AskPCExperts hereby disclaims any sponsorship, Affiliation or Endorsement of or by any such third party.
